Matthew Martinez

I have a passion for all forms of media. Utilizing technology, problem solving skills, and design to generate effective solutions should be the key focus of any good developer. I apply this ethic in all of my work efforts, utilizing my skills and observing industry trends to develop elegant and memorable user experiences.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lottery Marketing Specialist — The Florida Lottery, Miami FL

JUNE 2018 - PRESENT

Facilitate the day to day functions of the Miami Lakes district office, educate players on lottery games and rules, sell tickets, prepare daily and weekly settlement reports and provide customer service and assistance.

Motion Graphics Artist — Convention News Television, Orlando FL

DECEMBER 2017 - FEBRUARY 2018

Worked with the lead designer to create promotional videos for clients. Utilizing Premiere, After Effects, Photoshop, and Illustrator to develop aesthetic materials tailored towards the client's brand.

Inventory/Accounting Intenr — Edd Helms AC and Electric, Miami FI

JUNE 2016 - AUGUST 2016

Processed invoices, investigated discrepancies, organized and recieved inventory.

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Keyword — Password generator / manager

Keyword is an app that promotes the use of unique secure passwords across a users various accounts. Users would use this platform to link and save passwords to various accounts across any platforms for storage. This assists users with creating new and unique passwords for each account they register instead of reusing existing ones or repeating patterns. The primary feature involves a process that takes in user information, that they decide to share. This info could be personal or random and can be strings of digits, characters, special characters, combinations of either to produce unique passwords based on the the users "modifiers" to generate random combinations

https://github.com/matsui23/Keyword

EDUCATION

University of Central Florida, Orlando, FL — December 2017 Bachelor of Arts, Digital Media

LaunchCode, Miami, FL — March 2019 LC101 Programming Course and LiftOff Job Training



786-376-9867



mattgamedev2313@gmail.com



https://github.com/matsui23



www.linkedin.com/in/matthew-

martinez2313

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Java
- Pvthon
- Javascript

FRAMEWORKS

- Flask
- Spring

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- HTML
- · CSS
- Bootstrap
- MvSQL

